AnimeMusicQuiz.com PRIVACY POLICY
=================================

**Last Updated: October 15, 2017**

### 1\. Introduction

animemusicquiz.com is a social game platform that allows friends to compete against each other anime music knowledge and to provide social commentary based on their experiences (collectively the “Content”).. We respect your privacy and the security of your personal information, and we want to do as much as we can to protect it. Because of this, we have created this Privacy Notice to govern how we deal with your personal information. Since our Site is built off of Content that you provide, including shared information from third party sites, it is important that you read and understand their information sharing policies as well.

This Privacy Notice tells you when it was last updated, what information we collect from you, how we might use it, how you can review or change the personal information you provided to us, how we may change this Notice, and the steps we take to ensure that your personal information is protected. You are entitled to know once a year what information, if we share any with other businesses and for what purposes. Please request this information by contacting us at contact@animemusicquiz.com. By using the Anime Music Quiz Site, you consent that we may process the data that we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

All activities in which you may engage in with the Site are voluntary. You are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features on the Site which require such information. By submitting or otherwise making available your personal data or other sensitive information, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice and you expressly consent to the processing of your information accordance with this Privacy Notice. **If you do not agree with the terms provided in this Notice or our [Terms of Use](https://animemusicquiz.com/legal/tos), then you should leave the Site and should not provide us with any of your personal information.**

### 2\. Effective Date and Changes to this Notice

This Privacy Notice is effective as of the date above, and will remain in effect until a new Notice supersedes it. We may choose to update this Notice at our discretion, so you should review these terms periodically as the terms may change from time to time. The most recent version of the Notice will be reflected by the “last updated” date noted at the bottom of the page. Your continued use of the Site will constitute your acknowledgment of the Notice in its current version and your understanding of the terms of the Notice.

### 3\. Information We Collect

“Personal Information” means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, phone number, zip code, and e-mail address. “Non-personal information” means data about you that does not identify you personally. We collect Personal Information and Non-personal information, as described below.

**A. Personal Information** In order for you to sign up for our service, we ask for personal information from you including e-mail address and username from other social media sites. Your use of any of the video or chat features may be recorded or logged by our servers. We may use this data to improve our Site or Platform. We use the above referenced information to contact you regarding your account, assist in customer service and support, and to improve our Site and the animemusicquiz.com platform.

**B. Anonymous Information** We may collect information about you that does not identify you personally. When you access our website, we may collect such things as your IP address, browser, operating system, and other information that helps us know about the general nature of our visitors. We use this information to improve our Site and the animemusicquiz.com platform.

### 4\. Cookies and Other Data Collected

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience with the Site. Your Web browser may allow you to delete, block or otherwise disable the use of Cookies or HTML5. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of our Site may not work properly.

Web beacons and pixel tags are images embedded in a webpage or email for the purpose of measuring and analyzing usage and activity. Third party service providers acting on our behalf, may use web beacons and pixel tags to help us analyze usage and improve our functionality.

To make the Site and related services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third-party service provider) collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you, such as browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit.

We use tracking cookies to distinguish you from other users to help prevent one user from unwittingly logging into another user’s account on the same computer or network. We also use cookies to store setting preferences for the site, such as video volume.

Third party providers (eg. Google and Dailymotion) may also use cookies for providing their services. It is therefore important that you also read and agree to these providers privacy policy as well.

### 5\. User Content

We may allow you to post Content to our website, including videos and music. This content, once posted, is available for anyone to see and you are granting us the limited license for our use in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://animemusicquiz.com/legal/tos). As such, you must make sure you do not post anything that you do not have the rights to distribute.

### 6\. Third Party Sites

Since our Site is built off of Content and sharing, you can be sure that you will encounter links to third party sites or Content that is being displayed from a third party site. Anytime you encounter a link to a website outside of animemusicquiz.com, you should know that we have no control over that Site. We recommend that you consult those websites privacy policies, terms of service, and other similar documents when using them.

### 7\. Ways you might share your data

Anime Music Quiz does not sell your personal information or general information to third parties. However, in the future, we may provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties. For example, your data may be transferred to parties who assist in designing and operating the site, executing services, or helping us analyze collected data. These parties will only use your data for the purpose of carrying out the work as agreed with us and will be required to keep the information confidential. We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your personal information by service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control.

Your traffic and transaction information may be shared with our business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis. We may also draw inferences from this information, aggregate this information, and use this information to inform the operation of the Site, enhance your experience, or for any other lawful purpose. Such information shall be governed by this notice in the same manner as any other personal information.

We may host data with third parties and allow third parties to access, maintain, or otherwise use your information for purposes that we deem conducive to improving our business and service. We will strive to always deal with reputable providers, but we cannot make any guarantees. As such, you hereby agree that we are not liable for any privacy breaches that may occur as a result of the actions of third parties.

### 8\. Disclosure of Your Information for Security Purposes

Anime Music Quiz fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We will release personal or general information without your consent for security purposes, when required by law, or to prevent imminent harm to any person or entity. We will disclose personal or general information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, which may include responding to requests and court orders from jurisdictions outside Denmark. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful, as determined in our sole discretion. If we receive such a request we may, but are not required to, notify you of such request and give you an opportunity to respond.

### 9\. How Does Anime Music Quiz Keep my Data Safe?

Anime Music Quiz uses a combination of technical and administrative security controls to maintain the security of your data. In addition to physical security measures such as limiting the number of persons who have access to your information, Anime Music Quiz uses a number of technological security measures, including password encryption, to keep your information safe. If you have a security-related concern, please contact us at contact@animemusicquiz.com.

### 10\. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

The Anime Music Quiz Site it is not intended for users under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally gather personal data about visitors who are under the age of 13 and we do not allow users on our website who are under the age of thirteen years old. If you are aware of, or suspect that, someone under the age of 13 is using the Anime Music Quiz Site without permission, please notify us immediately by contacting us at contact@animemusicquiz.com. If we suspect that, or you are reported, as being in violation of our age policy, we may freeze your account and require that you submit satisfactory proof of age before you may continue using our service.

If you have questions or concerns about the Internet and privacy for your child, we encourage you to check out the [FTC Guidelines](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online) for protecting your child’s privacy online.

### 11\. Deactivating your account

You may deactivate your account at any time by contacting us at contact@animemusicquiz.com. When submitting your request, please let us know what led you to deactivate your account. Your feedback is greatly appreciated, and will help us to better accommodate members of the community.

### 12\. Questions or Comments

If you have any questions or comments relating to the Anime Music Quiz Site or this Privacy Notice, send an e-mail to contact@animemusicquiz.com.

* **Contact**

* **Social**

* **Legal**

2017 Next World Games ApS
